antiques-atlas.com 2019-12-21

# Antiques For Sale, UK Fairs Diary, Antique Shop/Dealer Directory and Antique Furniture - Antiques Atlas

## Privacy policy

This privacy policy sets out how Antiques Atlas uses and protects any information that you give us when you use our websites.

### Who we are

We're Antiques Atlas, our website address is: https://www.antiques-atlas.com, also https://www.antiquesatlas.com. It is Antiques Atlas' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

We take data protection and privacy very seriously and avoid collecting data where possible. Any data collected is used purely in the operation of the website. 

#### Enquiries to dealers

If you make and enquiry on the site we will collect the data shown in the enquiry form and also your IP address and browser user agent string to help with spam detection. Information on the contact form will be forwarded to the dealer in question. We will receive your email address but this will not be publicly shown on the website.

#### Contact forms

If you send us a message via the contact form, we will receive the data shown in the contact form as well as your IP address and browser user agent string to help with spam detection. We will only use the information supplied to reply to your message.

#### Members of the site

Anyone that has joined the site; submitted a listing, joined as a seller or subscribes to Email Alerts may be a member of the site. Data is collected to enable you to log in and use the Antiques Atlas services. This may include name, email address, IP address and an encrypted version of your username/password, contact data including billing address, email address and telephone numbers. If you interact with us through social media this may also include your social media user name. Transaction data may include details about payments to us, but this will not include credit card numbers. We may also collect usage data including information about how you use our website.

#### Email alerts

If you subscribe to the Email Alert service we will receive your email address, name and categories of interest. This information is used to send the Email Alerts. Data is held for the duration of your subscription to Email Alerts. You may change your Email Alert preferences at any time or unsubscribe at which point your Email Alert data will be completely removed.

#### Antique Fair Tickets

If you request a Fair Ticket we will collect your Email address, name and fair of interest.

#### Antique Business and Fair Listings

If you submit a business listing for inclusion on the site we will collect the data shown in the form. For the purposes of keeping it up to date and maintaining the accuracy of the directory, we will contact the antiques related business listing owners from time to time by email, phone or even post to check details are current, up to date and correct. At that time we may also provide details of additional related services on offer such as premium listings or other antiques related services that we feel may be of interest. 

#### Payment

No credit card transactions take place on the Antiques Atlas website. All payments take place via secure 3rd party partners. In these cases you will be subject to their privacy policies on their respective websites: paypal.com securehosting.com (Monek). We do not save, collect or retain any credit card details on the Antiques Atlas site.

#### Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics to track website usage and provide information such as referring websites and user activity on the website. Your IP address may be captured by Google Analytics, but no other personal information is stored.

#### Cookies

The website may use cookies, which are small data files stored in your web browser by the website. These cookies may be session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, or persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted. The website may use cookies to record information on which pages are visited.

You as a user may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies by using a setting of your internet browser. Any already set cookies may be deleted at any time using the settings in your internet browsers. However if you deactivate the setting of cookies, not all website functions may be usable or may function as intended. For more information about how to reject cookies using your internet browser settings please consult the "Help" section of your internet browser (or alternatively visit http://www.aboutcookies.org). 

### How we look after your information and how long we retain your data

We use appropriate technological and operational security measures to protect your information against any unauthorised access to or unlawful use. We will retain your information for as long as is necessary to provide you with the services that you have requested from us or for as long as the law otherwise permits.

If Antiques Atlas was sold or substantially all of its assets were acquired by a third party. User information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Antiques Atlas may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage users to visit this page regularly to check for any changes in our privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Enquiries may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Enquiries made to a dealer or an item of their stock will normally be forwarded to that dealer.

If you request a fair ticket, your email may be forwarded to that specific fair organiser, who may send you tickets for their future fairs. 

### How to contact us about your data

If you have any questions about the usage of your data on this website, or would like to know what data is held about you please contact us via the contact form. You have the right to have any or all of your data changed or deleted.
